hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jeremy
Krakowski and if you haven't met yet I
help coaches mentors trainers and
Consultants scale their businesses to
seven figures and I want to help you
break past what's stopping you if you
need to just make your first six figures
or you need to make your first sale I
help you go from zero to over a million
dollars in your business and that's what
this podcast is all about is helping
people that have a message and want to
impact people with those messages
whether it's with an online course or
with an online coaching program or an
online Consulting business to reach the
right clients to make a ton of money
doing so and to be successful and and if
that's you that's who this podcast is
designed for that's the people that I
connect with and the people that get the
most results out of this now if you're
listening to this just because you know
you're you're wanting to to learn and to
grow and and things like that you'll get
some value from this but this is
specifically for my business owners for
people that own a business or that are
building a business business and and
here's one of the number one things that
I need you to get okay we're just going
to dive right into it one of the biggest
things that stops people from being
successful as a as a business owner as a
coach as a course creator as a as a
mentor making money as a trainer making
money as a consultant making money
there's a there's a dividing line right
down the middle and I'm trying to find
my my marker here
there's a dividing line right down the
middle when it comes to
what those that are successful do
and one what those that are that
struggle and strive and and wish they
could be successful too so we have on on
one side of the board here
we have struggle
this is where most people are
99 of coaches
and then we have the one percent and
these are the ones that I work with
that have success
and we have a number of clients that are
in the middle here where they're
transitioning from the 99 that fails to
one to the ones that struggle
this one strategy that I'm going to
share with you today
will help you move the needle so much
closer into the realm of success
than anything else
[Music]
one of the greatest strategies is a not
worrying about what people think not
worrying about looking professional
sounding professional for instance just
an example recording this podcast when I
couldn't find this marker right here
some people would have ended their
podcast they would have restarted they
would have edited that out of it they
would have removed that from there
because it makes them look
unprofessional that extra work would add
an hour or two to their production cycle
I see it as a waste of time and the
return on my effort is just not worth it
to even worry about how I look or sound
to anybody okay so that's the number one
thing
I think if you can get over worrying
what anybody thinks about you and you
just talk and you just flow and and you
worry about how can I can communicate
with my target buyers the people that
are buying from me how can I communicate
with them to help them grow more often
that matters far more than looking like
a pro to them they don't care how you
look you listening to this right now
aren't offended and your reputation or
opinion of me isn't destroyed because I
didn't edit that out or even the fact
that I'm focusing on this right now you
see what I'm saying and so it's the
exact same way with your clients with
your customers anybody that you lose
because you're unprofessional quote
unquote wasn't meant to be a client of
yours in the first place okay now the
second thing is this is we have to break
up with this mindset of
I need to be told what to do
I need somebody to tell me what to do
this comes from
childhood what our parents tell us what
to do and when we do what they told us
we get rewarded this comes from
Corporate America when we do what we're
told we get rewarded this can come from
religious systems where we obey and
we're not punished and and and we end up
believing that success in business is
the same way
that's what 99 of people who struggle
think that if I just get told what to do
I will be successful
now yes if you're coaching with me if
you're working with me and we're going
back and forth about a topic on your
business and we're talking about okay
who's your Target customer and what do
you work with with them and and do you
have an offer up and and you already do
you have a niche figured out and we
answer those questions we go over those
five sticking points that coaches
trainers and mentors have whether it's
finding your Niche do you have your
Niche figured out yet if you don't start
there once you do it's writing your copy
do you have your copy written if you
don't then do that
next is do you have your landing page
done if you don't then do that because
you already have your Niche and your
copy figured out don't skip ahead to the
landing page and trying to figure out
all the technical stuff if you don't
even have your copy or your Niche
figured out yet
it's like it's it's really simple most
people over complicate it and they stay
in the struggle Zone because they're
trying to skip ahead and they're trying
to figure out step 789 when they haven't
even done step one yet because they they
have this anxious belief that if I
figure everything out beforehand then I
will be successful welcome to struggle
City
welcome to things not working out for
you
100 percent
and so when we work together and we
process through all of those those
different steps
okay you got your landing page up now
have you launched it have you told
people about it okay have you ran ads to
it okay
did you do the event and how did it sell
okay did you evaluate the data did you
run another offer another event and see
how that did did you evaluate the
response the feedback loop that you got
from people to adjust your language
this is this this is the circle that
when you do this consistently produces
profits produces results
okay
most people can't get past the stage of
even creating a landing page
most people
find it impossible
to even create a landing page
takes you 10 minutes on Squarespace
I have so many videos where I walk you
through how to do that to where you can
use Squarespace to to put a headline up
and you make a graphic in canva that you
have templates that you use it takes 10
minutes to build a landing page
but most people are terrified of the
idea that it might not work out it might
not be good enough they might be
rejected they might waste time they
might lose money and it might not
produce the results that they want and
they allow that fear and Terror of
things not going their way and the need
to make things go their way keep them
from building a landing page that's
where most people are stuck it's most
people's mindset are stuck right there
they can get right up to the point of
having a landing page to build
or writing their copy and they won't do
it they just won't they will literally
sit paralyzed I've seen it
six months 12 months
five years seven years I know somebody
right now
he's in his tenth year of being
paralyzed to write his copy and make a
landing page
because of his need for certainty
because of his need to be told what to
do and this is where most people
struggle is their need
four
their need for certainty
and to be told
what
to do
keeps them paralyzed from writing any
sales copy
from creating a landing page
from building an offer from Gathering a
group of people in front of them on a
zoom meeting to sell a 300 product to a
500 digital product to a thousand dollar
digital product too
this is the cycle where most people are
stuck
and it and it comes directly from the
mindsets of how we have been trained to
live our lives
for Safety and Security
up until this moment in time everything
in your life has trained you
that you are unsafe when things are
uncertain that you are unsecure that bad
things will happen
if there's no certainty
everything in your life has trained you
that until you are told what to do by
some kind of an expert out there
that you are unsafe that you that things
are uncertain that you're on Shaky
Ground that bad things will happen if
you do something that you weren't told
what to do
and and this is where 99 of course
creators and coaches are stuck
they're stuck operating in
seeking after certainty and being told
what to do
now because of this you can actually
capitalize on this and a lot of people
have capitalized on this because this is
actually a big part of what you're
selling to your clients this is a big
part of what you're selling to your
prospects
is the feeling of certainty the feeling
of that they will be told what to do
but at the end of the day
it's impossible for any coach any
trainer or any consultant no matter how
much what they know
to provide a hundred percent of either
of these in reality when you're selling
it's very important that you build a
level of belief perceived trust with
these to a hundred percent
and Jordan Belfort goes over that in the
book The Way of the wolf the
straight-line selling system mastering
the art of persuasion influence and
success is that it's that it's that it's
crucial that your prospects that your
prospective clients
feel in a in your sales pitch that level
of belief and certainty and that you are
going to be there to tell them what to
do when it comes down to it
what produces the top one percent of
success
is by graduating out of needing this and
by graduating out of the corporate
mindset by graduating out of the mindset
that there is anybody out there that
actually is even capable of doing this
for you
and so I'm going to be speaking to you
both from the perspective of you being a
coach you being a trainer you being a
mentor but also what you need to do to
get some sales is you need to first off
break up with this belief that's been
limiting you that certainty even exists
that's a fantasy
that's not reality
it doesn't exist
finding a human being to tell you what
to do
is a fantasy it is not reality
it doesn't exist
as soon as you get that you will start
to make more money
because you're going to stop looking to
other people
to be responsible
for your results
when we're searching for certainty and
to be told what to do we are looking to
make other people
responsible for the results because
here's the thing if so and so told you
what to do and it didn't produce a
result now they're on the hook for the
responsibility of what It produced
that's not reality in a corporate job
that's what they train you your boss is
responsible to tell you what to do and
if you do it there is certainty that you
get a paycheck
you have to rip that thing
out of your brain and it hurts when you
do so
because much of how we've lived our life
has operated in these Frameworks
and as soon as we say you know what I'm
going to take personal responsibility
for my life
I'm going to stop blaming other people
I'm going to stop looking to another
human being to be my certainty
human being to tell me what to do
you now unlock the keys to massive
financial success in your life
because you start looking at the world
differently
you start looking at how things fit
together differently
you start processing information
differently you start analyzing data
differently
when you do this and my clients who make
the most amount of money that I coach
here's the thing I would be a a an
irresponsible coach if I didn't tell you
this
there's a lot of coaches out there
that won't tell their clients this
because
they're afraid of losing clients when
clients actually realize how the world
works
I'm not afraid of losing clients
I want to make more of my clients
successful
and so by me being honest with you about
this
is part of my integrity
and the fact is
that in business there is no such thing
as certainty because the market changes
people change
the algorithms change on a daily and
weekly basis
there are certain Frameworks that work
better than others and I coach people on
those Frameworks that we use
consistently
running events where you get people in
front of you to sell to them your
programs is one of the most certain
Frameworks
for growing a six and seven figure
coaching Business course business
Consulting business right now doing
events whether it be a one day one hour
or a two hour or a multi-day a three-day
straight or a five-day event
virtual events getting people with the
problems you solve in front of you for
multiple days at a time is the most
certain framework
for financial success
but here's the thing when people join my
coaching program
I don't just tell them okay put these
words on your page and it's going to
work no
in fact that that would cost you over
sixteen thousand dollars to do because
it takes a lot of energy and research on
my part to to dive into your business
and so what I will teach you as a coach
is I will guide you to doing that
research I will guide you through the
process that we've developed that
produces results
if you wanted to pay me to do it it's
over 16 to 20 000 per month minimum
starting if you want me to tell you what
to do
you have to pay me that much to tell you
what to do
for my clients that are in the client
growth accelerator they're paying under
200 a month it's the closest thing to
that but I'm not gonna necessarily tell
them what to do I'm gonna guide them to
find it on their own because I expect
that the people that are in my programs
are grown up enough to do the research
themselves they're grown up enough to
take personal responsibility they're
grown up enough to start to change their
habits and to break out of the corporate
mindset of I need to be told what to do
and I need certainty before I take
action
when you get this
incredible results will start to follow
in your life because you will start to
take action on things you were never
told what to do
oh I got a hunch that this might work
great go test it out
go try it out
I mean this with all due respect but
I've had clients where they had a hunch
six months ago but they were nervous to
ask me for six months they asked me six
months later and I'm like honestly that
would have worked six months ago if you
had just done it when you had the hunch
but now six months later I don't think
it would work as well because honestly
the Market's changed
gotta go back to the drawing board
got to go back to evaluate what's
working what's not
and so if we're looking for
another person to provide peace and calm
and certainty and clarity
and and and
to tell us what to do
listen there's people out there that
that will be glad to take your money and
pretend like this is possible
for you
absolutely
but at the end of the day what is it
going to take for you to actually make
real money is taking personal
responsibility growing up out of the
corporate honestly like working a job
let's put it this way
there's a mentality
that is a level above high school
it's a level above college education
to where you work for somebody else
but there's somebody that you're working
for in a job who was an entrepreneur who
started a business
and so you have to graduate from job
worker mindset
to business owner mindset business owner
mindset never waits to be told what to
do is never looking for certainty and
always takes personal responsibility
job worker mindset is always waiting to
be told what to do is always looking for
the next most certain thing for Safety
and Security and refuses to take
personal responsibility
and so this is an area to grow out of
the job worker mindset the worker bee
mindset into the owner entrepreneur
mindset
of I'm gonna try things out I'm gonna
take risks I'm gonna experiment just to
see what works
and now here's going to be the hardest
the next hardest thing
on this level
and this is one of the number one words
that's going to make you a millionaire
is acceptance
when you learn
to accept
the outcome
whether it be a win
or a loss
when you say when okay great we won when
you say loss okay great we lost and it
does not affect you
emotionally
when your emotional stability when your
happiness
when your sense of self-worth when your
sense of accomplishment
is not dictated on performance
at all
and you learn to accept wins and losses
with the same level
of emotional feeling and response and
you and you and you you learn that
whether we win or lose it's okay it's
all good
it's part of the process
and you graduate to where instead of
losing you actually
are learning
see I don't I don't win or lose I win or
learn
Shawn White the Olympic snowboarder
actually came up with this that I heard
for the first time he might not have
invented it but I heard it on the on the
add to my let podcast by the way I love
Ed mylett as well he's got some great
personal development training out there
and but Sean White talked about this is
that
as an entrepreneur as an Olympic
snowboarder by the way there's huge
similarities to the way that you train
to the way that your mindset needs to be
you need to have
and
an Olympian
mindset
a lot of what I study when it comes to
business and it comes to mindset comes
straight out of what has worked in the
sports world and the Olympic coaching
world
because it takes the same level of
mental fortitude
as an Olympic athlete
form or the military
a a Navy SEAL
learning to strengthen your mind to
where your situations and how things
happen
don't decide for you whether you can be
tossed to and fro whether you have a
good or a bad day
and so when you get to this place of
acceptance
foreign
you don't get too like oh my gosh
when you win like you celebrate
but instead of just celebrating only
when you win or only the big wins you
celebrate progress
you celebrate your progression
you celebrate that you are one percent
better than you were yesterday that
you're one percent
from where you wished that you were to
where you want to be
freaking go all out and like pat
yourself on the back for that
amazing
and then you get back to work and you
get back to work not waiting for
somebody to tell you what your next
steps are not waiting to be told what to
do
instead choosing
to step up for yourself
choosing this Olympian mindset
choosing
to experiment choosing to take risks to
put yourself out there
even when it feels hard
that's going to set you up for Success
more than anything else
when we stop waiting for certainty when
we stop waiting for
somebody to tell us what to do and we
learn to adapt and we learn to say you
know what
I'm going to grow into that Olympian
mindset I'm going to grow into that
entrepreneur that owner mindset and out
of that job worker that worker bee
mindset not that those people are bad
not the people that work jobs are bad at
all
there's just a different way of thinking
when it comes to being an entrepreneur
and the same level of thinking doesn't
work in one or the other so you have to
literally completely rewire your brain
out of how you've always done everything
if you weren't an entrepreneur to see
success in your life
and that's what I want for you if you're
a coach if you're a trainer if you're a
mentor if you're somebody that is making
an impact on the world and you want to
make six figures or seven figures
it's time to start to do things
differently
and if you want somebody to help coach
you guide you through that that's what
this podcast is for that's what my
YouTube episodes are for
my client growth accelerator I believe
is the number one coaching program out
there for trainers mentors coaches
authors Consultants to get more paid
clients online and I'd love to help
guide you along the way as to what are
those nuances what are the Frameworks
that are working right now so that you
can start to see real cash flow and real
money in your business so you can go
check that out go go join the program if
it's not open right now you can get on
the waiting list to it at my website and
you can join one of the live events that
we're doing we do multiple events
throughout the month where we're working
with you and we're we're getting our
nose to the grindstone to help you with
the exact strategies that are going to
produce results and that's what we do
every single day here in my business
over at jeremykurkowski.com and that's
what I'd love to help you do as well I'm
on a mission to create over a thousand
millionaire coaches will you be one of
them grow your life everybody and we'll
talk soon have a good one